My name is Yasmin.
I am three months pregnant.
It is said that everyone is born equal according to the law.
That is not what happens in my world.
Who would want to be born between chaos and hatred?
I decided to protect my child from evil.
FRONTIER(S)
My choice...
In the second round of the Presidential elections?
A massive anger...
...By the actions of the police.
The riots started...
...Against the authorities of extreme right.
The situation worsens...
We're almost there, c'mon!
Not so fast!
Stop!
A little more.
- Not so fast. - OK.
Stop!
Alex, don't do stupidities!
- What are you doing, Alex?! - Stop!
Stop, Alex!
- Do not move! - Alex, stop, for fuck's sake!
Now what?! Stand up!
What's going on?
Did you think you were so tough?
Motherfucker!
- Let him be! - For fuck's sake!
Alex, relax!
Run, fast!
- What? - Sami is injured and bleeding!
What have you been doing?
Fuck!
- He's gonna die, your brother will die! - Let's take to a hospital!
No, wait for me.
Yasmin, do not do anything. Wait.
So we sit down and watch?
Can't you understand?! I said you to wait!
- You are an idiot, Sami is injured! - Is it my fault?
Sam wanted it.
- We'll go the three of us. - What do you think?
- They went away from us because you hurted her! - Yasmin is my girl!
Come on, be careful!
- Farid stop. - This is to remember.
We've arrived.
You have taken too much!
- Where were you? - The streets are filled with barricades.
We must take him away from here.
We don't need him.
- Isn't it risky? - Don't say anything about my brother.
- It was your fault! - And you?, were you on vacations?!
- Idiot! - Calm!
Well, think what we are going to do, okay?
- I'll bring him to the hospital! - They'll catch you.
You are right, but what if we don't carry him?
- It's not your decision? - Shut the fuck up!
Son of a bitch.
Tom, he needs a real doctor.
Well, this is what we'll do...
You go with Farid and then we will meet in a hostel near the border
I'll accompany them to the hospital. We will leave him and we will meet with you.
Okay.
I won't go with this idiot. I prefer to die!
It's over, motherfucker. Do what you want.
Please.
- Please, Farid Take me with you. - I can not.
I do not want to stay here.
What do you want?
- How do you feel? - I could be better.
What about the baby?
Now you care? You no longer cheat anyone.
- We can manage by ourselves. - Yas.
It's enough. I will abort and you'll be calm.
Do not do that to me.
I do it for myself.
Farid, you are a complete idiot. Do you want them to find us?
Quiet.
- How much? - 1125...
...plus this and this.
- I suppose you know that is not for us. - There's enough.
- What are you going to do with it? - Why do you want to know?
- It is necessary to decide something. - I am not yet dead, son of a bitch!
- She is good with the whole world. - Get in there!
Okay, can we go, boss?
Are you going to leave us?
Then we leave.
Good luck, Sami.
The authorities have decided an exemplary punishment
for the incendiary. The have sent more police.
Each detainee will be brought to the barracks overall for identification.
We will go faster by overthere. If you don't want to run.
- Shut the fuck up! - Hurry up, ok?!
Don't touch me!
- Can't you go faster? - It's enough!
Hold him.
Just her.
Son of a bitch...
Everything will be fine.
Hold, Sami, hold.
- What happened? - Help us, please, I beg you.
- What happened? - Haven't you been aware of the shootings in the city?
- Now I return. - Quick.
Hold.
Yas...
I'll take care of him.
Let the baby be born.
Is it worth...
Being a mother... without a future?
Fuck them all, it is not their problem. It's your life.
I love you, Sami.
I love you so much...
I love you, Yas...
I love you.
They're coming.
Go away quickly.
- I won't leave you! - You have something important to bring.
I won't leave you! No, no...
Go...
Hey you!
Please, we must ask you some questions.
Stop or we'll arrest you!
Stop!
It is done?!
Move!
- What the fuck happened there? - Move!
Stop!
Shit!
They almost grab you.
Your brother will sing. We are full of shit.
Sami won't betray us.
He died, Alex!
I want you to take me to my house.
I beg you.
I will not say anything, I swear.
That was not the agreement. Now we can not retreat.
- I am already calm. - Me too.
We are already well away.
Is this still France?
Yes, the deepest.
Is there any better place in this country than this?
Did you want to stay in the city?
Maybe.
I should have gone to my father's funeral with Bleude.
But I was late...
And I could not leave the district in time.
I said that if I walked out of there again I won't no longer return ever.
And there is nobody wait for me.
Not even a girlfriend?
Fool.
There's no girl behind.
- Why do we stop? - Shut up.
- What? - Get out.
Why?
Out!.
- Sorry, but the money stays with me. - What?
- But why? - I have said you to leave.
I want to relax in your seat!
It hurts me.
Stop, don't fool around.
- It's the last fucking time I ask you to leave! - Ok, I'm going out.
Don't panic, it was a joke.
We'll rest here.
Idiot.
Don't cry, you have to be a man.
Were you scared?
A little, motherfucker.
Hello?
Tom, it's me.
We are on the way.
No, it's okay. They have said that he'll survive.
Where are you?
Still three hours.
Until then.
Why haven't you said it to them?
There is no need to complicate it further.
You are not alone, We are all involved.
I feel sick.
I am going to puke.
I think I'll quit.
- Really? - My mother will behappy.
She'll believe that I have matured.
- I need to sleep. - Me too.
- What sets there? - "Rooms".
There is always something free in those sites.
Border> <Dachville 2.5 km
It costs money.
- Man, this is not Panama. - This is the perfect place..
Good site.
Good evening.
Is there any room for rent?
Here everything is possible.
- The rooms are free. - Then we will be your visitors.
How much do you have?
Much.
We will be two more.
- Is it possible a second room? - Three.
I must register you.
Goetz, a customers!
- I can not stand it. - Quiet.
Hey, Goetz, are you asleep or what?!
What's going on?
Is the number two ready?
How long?
One evening.
Ok, you can stay. Girls, take care of their lodging.
Thanks.
- A drink? - It will be a pleasure.
They won't belive we found this two beauties.
You're... incredible.
Very kind.
What's the matter with you?
Dude, this is rare...
You're so charming boys. You're a gift from heaven.
Do you have something to show us? We're losing time.
Won't you have forgotten it?
Here comes married people, but I see that you are very emotionally impulsive.
I assume he is the leader
Farid, don't tell that silly topics.
You are right, Gilberte.
I am impulsive.
I am impulsive here...
...And here too.
Aren't you ashamed?
No, no. I have a girlfriend.
What's going on? We must reach out to the end.
Dude, we have to drive tomorrow All day...
Enough of nonsense! This is something for adults.
Do we continue?
I see that you aren't getting bored.
At least they aren't pussies.
Gilberte, take them to the room.
Finish there.
- Are we going? - Me?
You wanted to finish.
Claudia, take care of the other...
We'll have a good time together.
We go up at once.
No, I am going to call my girlfriend.
I promised her.
You do not know what you're losing.
Shit.
Fuck, they're sweet.
Come here, I'm gonna fix you.
I'm ready...
Come, come, come...
I have girlfriend!
Dude, fuck her well!.
Leave me!
Be a man!
What's going on?
I did not think we would have this familiar meal so soon...
It's called "hospitality".
Pass the dishes.
Thanks.
Let's see what you have done in your kitchen.
It will be good to recover forces.
Really?
Delicious, what is it?
It is fried pork.
You won't freeze tonight.
It'll be good for you, you are decrepit.
Sorry, but I don't eat pork. My religion doesn't allow.
Are you Jewish?
No, I am Muslim. Just I do not like pork.
Girls help me.
Claudia, open her mouth.
Move away.
- Mom, make an effort. - Come on!
Mom, open your mouth.
Are you cheating us?
If you do not open, we no longer help you.
Do you understand?
Swallow, shit. I'm gonna get angry!
- Didn't she like the food? - What is all this for?
You treat your mother as a dummy.
We must help mom, or she'll lose the appetite...
Okay. Well, well.
- Are you tired? - I do not like these family reunions, but good profit.
- Hey, stay. - What's going on?
You were right, Farid. They are whores.
No, no, sorry... I's a joke.
He doesn't know what he's saying.
What's the matter with you? Are you sick or what?
She liked me to spank her ass...
And she even wanted more.
I told you that they were whores.
We went too fast.
It hurted me. She mattered to me.
Shit, Yas...
They'll kill us. Better don't say anything.
Really?
What's going on there? We won't arrive until another two hours.
Pretty good. What about you?
Everything was wrong.
We had problems at the hospital.
I understand.
- Are where are you? - In a small hotel, as we agreed..
I send you the address by SMS.
Don't say anything to Farid.
Understood.
See you, kisses.
Why do you whisper?
- Why are you scared? - For that people.
Fuck.
Damned whore.
Of these.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Newsflash.
The Minister of Interior is officially Candidate for the presidency of the Republic,
He's the subject of the protests.
Instability in the country mark presidential pre-campaign.
The police remains in state of maximum alert.
Fart!
I'I strangle them with my own hands.
For them.
Country of fascists.
France and the USA... Bush govern here for ten years.
What do you want?
Nothing. Somebody wants to see you.
Good evening.
- Do you know why I am here? - Not yet.
Where are you from?
From Paris.
So you're one of those who burn cars?
Will yo do the same thing here?
Were you lost down the road?
- We're driving to Holland... - I do not speak to you, idiot.
Now what?
He says the truth, we are going to Amsterdam to see some friends.
And...
You wanted to fuck.
You were looking for some whores.
And you came here...
Thinking that this was a brothel.
No, wait...
We are just normal people...
- Do you mean that my sisters are bitches? - No, no...
- Did you arrive to the end? - What?!
Did you? Don't you understand the question?
Did you? Answer.
Yeap...
Hands up.
Hurry!
What have we done?
- Gilberte told me that you have a bag with money. - This is madness.
Liar!
- It's there. - Gilberte, What do you say?!
This is our clothes, as you can see...
Goetz!
We are screwed, fast!
Tom!
Stop or I shoot you!
Freeze!
I said you to stop!
- I'll prepare the luggage. - Stop!
Tom, brother.
Do not move!
Goetz, you didnt't killed him!
Catch them!
Fast, to the car!
They're shooting!
They chase us!
Hurry, faster!
Drive faster!
Quick, burn the pedals!
Faster!
They're by our side! Quicker!
Watch where you go!
- What now? - To the left.
So what?
They left the road and fell by the bridge.
I took this.
Claudia!
Farid, help me.
Farid, I beg you, stand me up slowly...
Stand up, with care...
Slowly.
Carefully.
Quiet.
Where are we?
Are you OK?
- Good evening. - Good evening.
Some of our relatives stopped here.
Are family of Tom and Farid?
Are they here?
Not really, they went to another motel.
- Why they didn't stay here? - We have no vacant rooms.
Can you show us the way?
You can follow me.
Claudia, you won't join us, You wait.
Come on.
Why does she gives me orders?!
I can't stand that!
- Obey Gilberte. - I am not her dog.
Hold a little! Soon you'll occupy her site!
Karl!
Goetz! I blocked the road.
Get back fast, father does not like to wait.
Where are we? Where are we going?
I can't stand this smell.. Corpses.
Better hold, ok?
We should turn around.
Where to? to hell?
We'll try to cross it.
Will you go first?
Come on.
1,2,3...
Are you OK?
What is there?
I see some lights!
I think I will go behind you.
Hey what?!
Go, come on.
- Come on. - Shit, I can not breathe.
I can not. Come on.
I can not breathe.
A little more!
Tom, we almost arrived.
Go on.
- It's over, I'm stucked. - We've almost arrived.
- I won't give you more advice. - Neither myself.
- Tom try! - I told you I'm stucked!
I'm stucked, fuck!
Mom, where are you?
Mom, I'm dying...
Mom!
Tom, only a little bit more. Go.
No!
Shit, you will be a man or a pussy?!
I'm stucked!
Go, c'mon! An effort!
¡Ahead!
- Go ahead Tom! - We almost arrive...
Come on!
Tom...
Hurry!
Faster, for fuck's sake!
Quick!
There's someone behind us!
Come on!
Fuck!
Go out, Tom.
- At the end of the road, right. - In what hole are we?
Those were miner wells. They were closed at the beginning of the century.
Do not be in a hurry.
I will notify that you have arrived.
No!
Begone!
Don't pay attention to her. She's sick.
Good evening.
Sit down.
Thanks.
Claudia, boil some water.
This is for hunters.
They organize good hunting parties.
Where are you heading to?
Towards the Netherlands.
We have some business there.
Do you have a towel, please?
Yes.
I will bring it to you.
- Are you married? - We are no longer together.
There is a small door.
SURGICAL ENCYCLOPEDIA
Are you hungry? Do you want something to drink?
Not. Thanks.
Come here!
Quiet!
He's coming.
Claudia, help me.
- Who comes? - Father.
Stay straight, he dislikes people who relaxes.
We welcome you, lady of the road.
What's your name?
Yasmin.
Irhant.
Your hand.
Go away...
Tom!
Go outta here...
Run...
Don't stop...
- What's going on? - Get up.
- What? - We leave.
- What happened? - Let's go to the car.
What is this?
- Okay. It is enough. Our friend was killed there.
Alex!
Yas!
Karl!
Bring him to the grill and cook him with fat.
Listen, son...
We must renew the blood of the family.
But I have doubts.
I do not know if she is appropriate.
She has a too dark complexion.
That hair, the eyes...
She does not have pure blood,
But we have no other choice.
You need a wife to occupy my seat.
She will be your wife.
Remember to protect the race.
Eve, bleed him, I'll finish him later.
- I will see what's happening over there. - They are the children.
Are your children loose by the mine again, right?
I will see what happens.
Surely there's a good meat.
I will go with you, Claudia.
Pull!
Stop!
Hurry!
Shit.
Stop!
Look in the engine room.
Hey little, where are you?
Where have you hidden, little?
Fuck you, bastard.
I won't leave you, Alex.
Yas...
Run for help.
- Seek help! - No!
No!
Go!
Go away!
I said you to go.
Hurry!
Fast!
Move away.
Cross.
Open!
Open it!
Run.
What's going on with you?
Hurry!
I love you.
Escape quickly.
I said you to go away.
Not yet.
Go.
Go now!
Quick, do not be afraid!
Cross.
Go and give notice.
Do not you confront with anyone here.
Open!
Out, move!
Where is the girl?
Screw you, fucking Nazi!
What did you say? Fast!
Bring me the pliers.
Don't...
What are you going to do?
I will make sure that you won't walk again.
Hold.
So...
In Africa, the guards did the same to diamond seekers
to remove the desire to escape for a long time
loaded with some brilliants.
Not yet...
Almost...
Finished.
This is the time of pain...
And the thieves were still working.
They worked!
They worked free!
Stop!
I beg you to help me!
I must call the police!
Come in, lady.
This is the wrong road.
Not. I'm taking you home.
No!
Quiet!
Close!
Leave it closed!
Shut up!
Not...
Hans!
Yas!
Superb.
You have a last wish.
Talk.
Finish me.
For the family!
Remove it.
You have successfully pissed me off.
Take him, Hans, for conservation.
Let's wash her.
You are pregnant.
That's great...
This will give you heat.
You will be soon a member of the family.
You'll sleep in my quiet room until you're ready
Is it okay?
What do you think?
I know...
I have something that can help.
We are very similar.
Father is happy You are pregnant.
Drink.
Everything will be more bearable.
This helps me when I make children.
Give me.
Is it strong, isnt't it?
Take.
- More, quick. - No.
In your state you have to be more carefully.
It's beautiful.
You have to cut it.
Father doesn't like black hair.
Father said that we are a unique breed.
We arrived here after World War II.
I was stolen from my parents when I was small..
They promised me that my parents will come if I was obedient.
Father wants you to madure quickly to bring babies.
Now I am the bride of Hans.
Our children are born sick.
They are deformed.
I'm expecting the fourth, but father said that is by our blood.
Why don't you escape?
I still hope that my parents will come to visit me.
They promised.
I know that they will come.
Good children aren't abandoned.
I know what I am talking about.
I love children.
Father wanted to get rid of them in the gas chamber.
Before father did that, Hans and I hid them.
Now they're living in the mine's tunnels by the side of the farm.
Sometimes I visit them.
I'd die here without them.
Here is our guest.
We ask you to sit.
Sit all of you.
For the new mother,
For our happy and wonderful family.
And the next and happy event..
For the birth.
If she's a girl she'lll be named Lilith.
If he's a child he'll be named Karl, like his father,
who now will join our dear and beautiful Yasmin.
This wil be a good year of great achievements.
Everyday you'll listen the sound of the wind of victory.
It is time to announce that I have decided to trust the care of our family
to my only son, whom I am proud of, Karl Von Geisler.
I ask you to stand up.
Thank you, father, This is a great honour.
From now on, you all will respond of your words and actions,
before your brother, my son, Karl.
You all must help my beloved daughter, Gilberte.
This goes especially for you,
Hans.
It seems that you were good friends.
You are sick.
It seems that you need more help than me.
Gilberte, my beloved daughter,
Can you explain to the lady the fate that awaits her?
As I said, we wait for the the child of the lady
As a sign of providence.
Besides,
he's the only unborn member of our great race.
No way.
Be friendlier with father you need to respect him.
You won't teach me what to do!
What a great authority of the new commander.
Goetz!
Karl!
Tell her to stand up.
Stand up!
And now...
This will be your sole and new family,
So put an end to these unnecessary disputes.
For the pure blood!
Let me go!
- Leave him! - Let me go!
Don't come closer or I cut his throat!
You open the door!
- Put the shotgun away! - I'll shoot you two!
I will make you bleed and die as a pig!
Hans, lower the gun! It's an order!
Do it, Hans?
Hans, idiot! Lower the weapon, I order you!
- Lower the weapon or I swear I cut you! - Hans, listen to her!
I'm not scared of you, slut! Neither of you!
Hans, don't!
Don't die.
Kill her!
Karl, here!
- We will go by a secondary way. - Wait at the main entrance.
Fucking monsters.
I can feel you.
Show yourself I said!
Little bitch...
Whore, where are you?
Bitch, I'm gonna chop you.
Do you want me to disembowel you?!
Do you want me to kill you?!
Come here!
Why do you want me to hurt you? Because you are the wife of our commander,
And now you decide, don't you?
So tell me what I do!
You redneck whore face!
I am more important than you!
Me!
Right now I will count on you.
Bitch!
Who chose you?
Here I command!
Only me!
You must obey me!
Come back here! I order you!
Don't you hear what I say?!
The old man invented everything... Why does he decide who commands?!
It's clear who commands! I command!
I command here!
Do you get it?!
Who did he appoint him? why did he choose him?!
I am the commander, I command!
So you should show respect!
Look at me when I speak, slut!
Look at me!
Fucking whore!
Drop that, do you hear me?
Drop it, I said!
This is what you wanted...
I... Wanted your help...
- Eve, you come with me. - No.
I can not abandon the children.
Escape.
They are seeking you. I'll say that I have not seen you.
Go! Hurry!
Claudia, she's here!
Claudia!
The two together!
Is this enough!
Go away
Is it the end?
Is it because it's the end?
- Begone! - Do not do that!
- Move away! - Don't!
Eve, move away!
- Don't! - Idiot!
Bitch, on your knees!
- Gilberte don't do that! - You are dead!
- We'll leave. - No.
Here are my children.
The disturbances related to the second round of presidential
frustate the access to the power of the candidate of the extreme right.
Yesterday afternoon, after announcement of the results, that was visible on his face.
The police is still in a state of maximum alert..